THE CHARACTERS, INSTITUTIONS
COMPANIES, AND PLACES
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTIONAL
Why didn't you go watch the movie?
EPISODE 8
I wanted to see you.
Are you the same Eun-ho that I know?
Why did you call me?
I resented working late alone.
I'm
used to being by myself.
I thought
that feeling lonely was a luxury.
I must have missed the warmth.
On the day I went to your house,
for the first time,
my house felt cold.
I was so used to it
that I didn't know it was cold.
I must have forgotten
that a home could be warm.
Isn't it strange?
The things I took for granted
before meeting you,
I can't take them for granted anymore.
But,
strangely enough, I liked that.
Dating at work without keeping
personal life and work separate.
It's not something I would do.
But I failed, which serves me right.
What? Why are you looking at me like that?
Ms. Kang.
You never seem to run away from anything.
Just like when
you confessed to me.
I'm not good at keeping things to myself
like a certain someone.
So, you didn't like it?
I liked it.
I never thought I'd be able
to like someone again.
I was completely preoccupied
with my child.
I didn't think
there was space for another.
But my heart fluttered a lot.
So I tried to fight against it,
but I failed, too.
I understand.
I'm full of charm.
Eun-ho.
Let's not overthink things.
Let's just consider our feelings
for each other.
I will treat you well.
I like you a lot.
Me too.
Why do you keep
looking at me like that?
Stop worrying and drive.
So this is what you look like
from the side.
Not bad.
Don't get out.
If you do, I might not let you leave.
I'm going.
Show me your forehead.
Close your eyes.
Done.
Byeol.
Yes?
Byeol…
How would you feel
if I had someone that I liked?
Dad, did you get a girlfriend?
I'm curious about your thoughts.
I'd be happy.
Dad, I'm already seven years old.
I'm not a kiddo.
I like it when you smile a lot.
Dad, I'm sleepy.
ONE FINE SPRING DAY
I'm sorry
about telling you
to muster up the courage.
Don't be sorry.
I can't stay heartbroken forever.
It's better that…
It can't be me, right?
No matter how urgent it is,
if you like a person,
you wouldn't cancel your date
with them, would you?
I mean,
that… depends on what happened.
Maybe something really urgent
came up at work.
Is that so?
Oh, man.
I'm getting my hopes again.
Look at you.
Your unrequited love is serious.
You say it like you're not the same.
Compared to you, I am…
not better.
We're pretty much the same.
The person I like
doesn't see me as a man.
She probably still sees me
as a high school student.
When he's with me,
he only talks about our children.
I shouldn't have suggested
being parenting friends.
I look at her every day at work,
but she looks at someone else.
You work together?
- Then you have to see her every day.
- Yes.
So? Did I win?
I'm the more unfortunate one.
I send the kids to school every morning.
Tomorrow as well.
- Really?
- Yes.
The day after he stood you up?
Yes.
That's intense.
I hate my father.
That's why she sees you as a kid.
Come on, you aren't going
through puberty anymore.
No, it's not like that.
Seriously,
I just don't understand.
Even after
the death of his own child,
how could he…
I must be drunk. What am I saying?
I'm sorry.
I won't remember anything since I'm drunk.
Say everything that you want to say.
You know what?
I miss my older brother.
My brother…
He really was
a good and kind person.
He was completely different from me.
But…
he died too young.
I don't know why
the good ones cross over so early.
Me neither.
I haven't found the answer yet.
My sister and her husband passed away
in an accident.
I asked the question many times
while holding the child
who was looking for his parents.
But I just couldn't find the answer.
Why are we similar this way too?
I know.
In that case,
is your son…
Yes, he's my sister's son.
However, no matter what others say,
he's my son now.
I'm always worried
about not being a good mom.
Since I'm not his mom by blood.
I started making picture books
thanks to Seo-jun.
I have stories
that I want to tell Seo-jun.
Honestly,
he must be an idiot.
Why doesn't he recognize
such a good person like you?
Right? That's exactly what I'm saying.
It's his loss for not being with me.
Agreed.
- Let's drink to that.
- Okay.
Cheers.
I'll pour you one.
Thank you.
You came racing in here earlier.
I thought you knew how to fly.
I have wings on my back.
Oh, really?
Yes, you haven't seen them?
They sure weren't visible.
If you're kind, you would see them.
- Cheers.
Su-hyeon.
I'm really sorry about yesterday.
Did you get home safely?
Yes, you should be sorry.
Canceling our date. Wasting our tickets.
You were a bit cruel.
Right?
Yes, I was being cruel.
Curse at me all you want. I'll take it.
If you're really sorry,
buy the tickets next time.
Would that be enough?
I'd be more than happy to.
And Su-hyeon,
let's go to the movies
with our kids next time.
They like movies, too.
Right, they do.
Daddy Yu.
That urgent thing last night…
Did it have to do with Ms. Kang?
What?
Yes.
I see.
I had a feeling that it was.
Oh, Byeol.
That's dangerous. Don't… Gosh.
Wait.
- Hello.
- Have a good day.
- Oh, hello. Have a good day.
- Hello, Mr. Yu.
- Hello.
Doors are closing.
Can we keep our relationship
a secret at work?
- Yes.
- At work, be strict about it.
Keep personal life
and work separate, okay?
You have a meeting
with Lawyer Jang Sun-woo at 1 p.m.,
Jaein Pharmaceuticals at 4 p.m.,
and Gloss Apparel at 5 p.m.
Is there more to report?
No, but…
Shall I lower this?
Mr. Yu.
Do it right.
Don't make it obvious.
Okay.
Just go out.
Why would I lower the blinds?
That was a bit embarrassing.
Eun-ho,
did you do something wrong with Ms. Kang?
She looks particularly cold
with you today.
Times like these
call for some special caffeine.
That's right.
Eun-ho.
Ms. Kang is strict about keeping
her personal life and work separate.
Ha! That goes without saying.
Isn't it good?
All right. Keep it, Eun-ho.
It hurts to see you heartbroken.
Kyung-hwa.
Work hard today.
Oh my gosh.
The statute of limitations has passed,
so they're less likely to file
a lawsuit again.
Yes.
Okay, I'll call you again. Thank you.
- Hello.
I don't have much time,
so I already ordered.
I don't have much time to eat.
Is that all right?
- Yes, I heard.
- Okay.
- We can talk while we eat.
- Sure.
Mikang Law Firm chose me?
I heard that they were deciding
between me and someone else.
Both of you are experts
in administrative litigation,
which is what
Mikang Law Firm is looking for.
They took a long time
to make their final decision.
In the end, what moved the firm was--
It must be my success rate.
Big law firms are also obsessed
with success rates.
No, it was your leading cases.
You've handled many cases that challenged
and interpreted the law in new ways.
Mikang Law Firm wouldn't overlook
someone like you.
Then that makes it easier
for what I'm about to say.
I'll be willing to change jobs
under a few conditions.
- Conditions?
- Yes.
Starting from 4 p.m.,
I will work from home.
Except when I have trials.
I'd like to reduce
the delegation work by half.
I'd also like a minimum
of two junior lawyers to myself.
May I ask why?
Work and life balance?
I'd like that in my life.
As you say, if I'm a candidate
that can't be overlooked,
such an investment
won't be too much to ask.
In return, I promise you
a high success rate.
I need to get this. Excuse me.
It won't be easy to negotiate.
Has Ms. Jang said anything else to you?
No.
There must be a reason behind
her sudden change of attitude.
Find out if she's in contact
with other search firms or employers.
Yes, ma'am.
When someone known to be a workaholic
suddenly wants work and life balance,
there must be a reason.
KIJIN NOODLES
I sent it all to your email.
Please take a look at it.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
If you can reply in time…
We should go too.
Shall we return to the office?
No, let's have some coffee first.
I'll look for a coffee shop nearby.
Aren't we going?
You shouldn't behave like this
during work hours.
- We're not at the office.
- It's still business hours.
It's because you're very strict--
Did I upset you?
Of course not.
You were absolutely right.
From now on, I'll be more strict
about keeping it a secret.
Why do you keep holding my hand
while saying that?
We're not at the office.
Exactly.
- Mocha salt bun?
- Great.
Why does she look so resolute?
Did it go well?
Gosh, what was that?
Why are you out here?
The meeting.
Weren't you at the meeting
with Lawyer Jang Sun-woo?
Yes.
Did it go well?
Yes, it went well.
Things went well.
Come on, Yu Eun-ho.
He's so adorable.
What are you doing?
What?
Who, me?
Didn't you just…
My head…
- You have a headache?
- Yes.
I'll bring you some medicine.
But…
I definitely saw her do this.
"So adorable?"
Wait…
Who?
I wonder if Ms. Jung is okay.
WRITER JUNG SU-HYEON
FREE SPIRIT
The sky is spinning.
Are you okay, Ms. Jung?
He's a light drinker.
WRITER JUNG SU-HYEON
Thank you for yesterday.
WAKE UP DRINK
I should be the one to thank.
For listening to my useless stories.
Why do we drink every time we meet?
He's a fascinating person.
He makes me spill my heart out.
Yes?
Is your work going well?
Yes, it's going well.
- Have some of this.
- Leave it there.
I'll eat while I work. Thanks, Mom.
What's with that curious look
on your face?
Ask away if you have questions.
Well, I'm just so frustrated.
I gave you time to go on a date,
but Eun-ho got back earlier than you.
You crawled back home extremely drunk.
What happened? Did it not go well?
Mom, breathe while you talk.
Exactly!
Answer me before I run out of breath.
Did it go well or not?
We didn't see the movie,
and we won't be seeing
each other in private.
So stop getting your hopes up.
It took place in 2021.
Blaming the authority's error
in the procedure,
it was decided
that it didn't violate the law.
Then we got it.
Good. Okay.
Then this will be our focus.
Ms. Jung, don't you need
to check your phone?
It's been ringing for a while.
- Can you give me the document?
- Here you go.
Gosh, I can't work. Excuse me.
I'm sorry,
but I need to go.
Find out if there are similar precedents.
I'll take a look in the evening.
I'm sorry!
Okay, see you later.
The person you called isn't available…
It's going to voicemail.
It's already been 30 minutes.
- Is she not picking up?
- No.
I sent her a message,
but she isn't responding.
She's so different from how I know her.
I can't tell what's real.
Have you contacted her office?
Thank you. One moment.
Ms. Jang.
Gosh, I'm so sorry.
One second.
Tae-yoon.
Let's talk upstairs.
There's an important trial this afternoon,
so no one's at the office.
I'm sorry for not showing up.
Something came up.
I think we should know what happened.
May I ask what happened?
We've filed for divorce,
and I'm fighting for custody.
He's attacking me
for neglecting our child due to work.
So I absolutely need time with my child.
Then the reason you asked
for those conditions…
Yes.
At my current job,
I'm in charge of many cases.
My husband is well aware of it.
I'll reduce work at a new firm.
I'm making an effort.
I need to show that to gain an advantage.
Their argument is…
he couldn't help having an affair
because I neglected family over work.
And in the process
our child wasn't properly cared for.
Today, the babysitter
suddenly called in sick.
But I have no one else
to take care of him,
so I decided to look after him today.
I'm back in the office
with my child again.
It's impossible not to work.
Yes, that's right.
But…
I could've reduced the amount.
After giving birth,
I didn't want to give up on my career.
I was overly ambitious.
But in the end,
neither work nor parenting.
I'm not doing anything properly.
As my husband says,
I may not have the right to be a mom.
There's no way to take care of my child.
Was it right to be ambitious?
Should I take custody of my child
to fulfill my ambition?
I always find solutions
for other people's cases,
but I'm lost when it comes to mine.
Of course you have the right.
Raising a child is not easy.
Enough that you want to abandon it all.
But you didn't.
You're trying your best
to keep your job and your child.
That's already impressive.
No parent starts off
with all the qualifications.
Even if it's lacking,
you try your best to do better.
It's the same for you…
as well as me.
You have the right.
Byeol, it's okay.
Eun-ho.
Let's get a divorce.
Seeing Byeol in your arms
suffocates me.
I guess it would be hard
for Ms. Jang to change jobs?
Even if I explain the situation,
the client won't accept it easily.
By the way,
why aren't you asking me?
You must be curious.
I am curious,
but it could hurt you.
You didn't ask me either.
She had a difficult time.
She said that she was suffocating,
so I couldn't stop her.
You don't resent her?
I did at first.
Now, I barely remember.
Do you keep in touch?
I've never contacted or heard from her.
Does Byeol know?
I was hoping that she wouldn't,
but she figured it out as she grew up.
However,
Byeol has never made it obvious.
After what happened, we were at a loss.
That oblivious, little child
grabbed my finger.
Very tightly.
Then I got a grip on myself.
I've been living since
with that sense of responsibility.
Instead of me raising Byeol,
she's the one who raised me.
I should be grateful to Byeol
for raising you to be so amazing.
One of the two people
who brought me where I am now is Byeol.
Who's the other person?
It's quite a long story.
I'll tell you next time.
So, you agree that you're amazing?
Well,
I'm not so bad, aren't I?
You don't know, do you?
"Not bad?"
You're incredibly amazing.
You're blushing.
All of a sudden…
You must be pleased.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello, Eun-ho.
I met someone who remembers
about the fire accident.
- Really?
- Yes.
I got the person's phone number.
I'll send it in a text message.
You should give a call.
Okay, sir. Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
- No problem.
Eun-ho.
Come on.
Mikang Law Firm picked a new candidate.
Contact Lawyer Ahn Jong-min.
Got it.
What should we do with Ms. Jang?
It can't be helped.
It won't be easy to find a law firm
that can meet her conditions.
I'll call her.
Is there more you want to say?
About Ms. Jang.
What do you think of her
as an in-house lawyer
In-house lawyers come to work
at a regular time.
Compared to law firms,
there are fewer cases and trials,
so the work is easier as a parent.
When getting her a new job,
we can't take her entire
personal life into account
just to be thoughtful.
Right.
I understand.
There has to be an offer.
Is there an offer for an in-house lawyer?
She's competent.
Helping competent candidates
work at the right place.
That's our job.
Is that the list of search offers?
I'll search more to find a place
that fits Ms. Jang's expertise.
Aren't you glad that I said yes?
Let's narrow down the list
and meet the person in charge.
We can give high fives, can't we?
You may go.
DODAM BOOK STORE
Uncle,
I think Dad found someone that he likes.
- What?
- Why are you so surprised?
I'm not.
I'm not surprised.
How did you find out?
There's evidence.
Evidence?
How do you know that word?
First.
He looks at the mirror a lot these days.
Second.
He has his phone on him all day long.
What is it?
Is your hair getting in the way?
Yes.
Dad, this isn't my hair tie.
I bought a new one.
Third.
He had another woman's hair tie.
What kind of daughter is Eun-ho raising?
Byeol, I think
you're the smartest seven-year-old
I have ever seen.
This is no big deal.
Right, no big deal.
By the way,
what do you think?
About what?
That your dad likes someone.
Are you against that?
I told Dad that I'd be happy.
Oh, did you?
I'm so proud of you, Byeol.
Uncle, when you find out who it is,
you have to tell me.
- Promise?
- Okay.
I promise.
DODAM BOOK STORE
The weather sure is nice.
Wanna go for a beer?
Why are you in such a good mood?
Did you win the lottery?
Winning the lottery
isn't anything special.
When someone that I like is happy,
that's winning the lottery.
That's because
we've never won the lottery.
What's going on?
- It's about Eun-ho.
- Yeah?
- I think he has a girlfriend.
- Really?
That's amazing. What great news!
Eun-ho should be going on dates.
Few days ago, he was hesitating
and couldn't muster up the courage.
I'm proud of him.
It's about time that he's happy.
You're practically Eun-ho's mother,
aren't you?
When did he have time to meet someone?
He always seems to
be with Ji-yun these days.
You're right.
Could they be…
What? That's ridiculous.
Why do you keep bringing them together?
It's possible.
They make a nice couple.
You're being weird.
Why can't they be together?
Ji-yun is single,
- and Eun-ho…
- What about him?
Anyway, it couldn't be her.
Ji-yun has been asking me
to change her secretary…
What? What is it?
Darn it. Let's get some beer.
Wait, what?
Don't step over the line at work,
Mr. Yu Eun-ho.
I'm off work, Ji-yun.
He's getting more and more shameless.
I'll get off work too.
I'm hungry.
Goodness.
Going up.
Doors are closing.
Darn it.
Why are we here early in the morning?
You…
Let me cure my hangover first.
I drank because of you, so you buy.
Thank you.
Did you add pickles and olives?
You care about that even now? I did.
- Twice the sauce too?
- Yes.
Ji-yun, you know…
It's not true, right?
What's not true?
I don't get it.
You left out the subject and object.
Say it properly.
You and Eun-ho,
- are you--
- Yes.
I like Eun-ho.
What are you going to do?
Are you really seeing him?
Is that not allowed?
Hey, I know that Eun-ho is a good person.
Of course, I know that.
But still…
Why are you choosing
such a difficult path?
Because I like him.
Do I need another reason?
So why do you like Eun-ho, of all people?
You've been lonely for so long.
You finally found someone
to rely on, but why…
is it a man with a kid?
What?
Call me a snob if you want.
Hey.
I know what kind of life you had.
Without parents,
you moved from relative to…
Ji-yun.
I just want
you to meet someone without flaws
like other people
and have a normal relationship.
I know what you mean.
But Mi-ae,
why is that a flaw?
That's his life.
I like Eun-ho as he is now.
I like him for having the life he led.
So don't say that anymore.
Gosh, I really don't know what to do.
If you don't know, stay quiet.
I'll handle it.
For now, pretend you don't know
anything at work.
Don't say anything weird to Eun-ho.
You've really gone
over the deep end for him.
Welcome.
Are you alone?
Mister, please take me to this address.
What is this about?
I know that Mikang Law Firm's
offer has ended.
Is there a problem?
Am I responsible for something?
No, I want to recommend you
another job offer.
No, it's okay.
I'm preparing to leave my current job.
I won't be working for now
to fully take care of my child.
Are you quitting work entirely?
Is it because of the custody lawsuit?
You must know that quitting your job
won't help you win custody.
It could work against you.
Yes, I know.
He will attack me by saying
that I can't take care of my child
without financial means.
When I work, I don't have time
to care for my child.
When I don't work,
I have no financial means.
They say I have no right to be a mom.
I really did try my best,
trying to make both work.
All this to keep my child.
Tae-yoon said
he'll go with his dad.
He wants to live with him.
But I refuse to hand him over.
I'll keep him with me.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Tae-yoon isn't home yet?
He should be been back from his tutors.
Okay, I will call him.
Why isn't he picking up? Where did he go?
What should I do?
He must have gone to his dad.
Well…
Ms. Jang, please calm down.
Hello.
I'm here to see CEO Kang Ji-yun.
So you're Ms. Jang Sun-woo's son?
Yes.
Do you want this?
Thank you.
How did you find this address?
I got Ms. Kang's business card
from my mom's office.
- That's amazing.
- You're smart.
You deserve the yogurt drink.
- Wow.
- Tae-yoon.
What happened?
I was worried about you.
I have a favor to ask of Ms. Kang.
Me?
Yes.
What's the favor you want to ask me?
Please let my mom work.
Tae-yoon, what do you mean by that?
I heard last time in the office.
That you can't work because of me.
I don't want you to quit your job
because of me.
Today, the babysitter
suddenly called in sick.
But I have no one else
to take care of him,
so I decided to look after him today.
I'm back in the office
with my child again.
After giving birth,
I didn't want to give up on my career.
I was overly ambitious.
Neither work nor parenting,
i'm not doing anything properly.
As my husband says,
I may not have the right to be a mom.
If I wasn't here,
you can keep working.
Is that why you wanted to be with Dad?
I interfere with your life.
- That's why.
- Tae-yoon.
Tae-yoon, that's not true.
Why would you?
Tae-yoon's the best.
I live because of you.
You're the reason
why I live.
Don't I bother you?
Then can I live with you?
Of course.
I really want to live with you.
Tae-yoon, if that's your favor,
we will be able to help.
This mister found a great position
for your mom.
She can work and still spend
time with you, Tae-yoon.
HIRING IN-HOUSE LAWYER
AT TAESEON ELECTRONICS
Taeseon Electronics is looking
for an in-house lawyer.
In-house lawyer?
Yes.
The salary will be lower than now,
but the company is highly interested
in land development.
It will help you expand your expertise.
The working hours are short and regular.
You'll be able to spend
a lot of time with Tae-yoon.
Take your time to think about it
and call us.
Thank you for the nice offer.
I'll try to keep my work and my child,
both under my care.
I'll be cheering for you.
I'll be cheering for you too. Good luck.
Stay strong, Tae-yoon.
- Thank you. Bye.
- Please take care.
That's nice.
How cute.
Good job.
YU EUN-HO
What are you doing? Did you get home safe?
- Hello?
- You weren't asleep?
No, not yet.
What were you doing?
I just put Byeol to bed.
Is she sleeping well?
She falls asleep as soon
as her head touches the pillow.
She doesn't take after me in that way.
How does it make you feel?
Are you sad to find out
she's different from you?
No, it's actually a good thing.
It'd be heavy
if she takes after me completely.
If she does something wrong,
I'd feel responsible.
You don't need to worry about that.
Byeol is much cleverer than you are.
Parents worry over nothing.
Including Ms. Jang.
Children are growing up just fine.
Right, we seem to worry too much.
Do you still have a hard time
falling asleep?
See that? You're worrying again.
Since when did it become so hard?
It's been so long that I don't remember.
Do you have nightmares?
Well,
my late dad always appears in my dreams.
You must miss him a lot.
Not really.
I don't miss him that much.
To me, he wasn't a good dad.
Shall I read you a book?
Didn't I say that I'm not a child?
This book is also for adults.
A super boring one.
It works like a sleeping pill.
How boring is it?
Go ahead and read it.
You won't be disappointed.
But a little later.
- Later?
- Yes.
Isn't the book next to you?
That's not it.
I want to talk to you longer.
Are you tired?
No.
I'm not tired at all yet.
I can't believe
the boring book didn't work.
I'll read you a heartwarming story
this time.
Starting with a good line.
"Consolation may not be something
that comes to you."
"It could be something
that you search for."
"I must get closer to consolation."
"I have to initiate the conversation
with consolation."
"The thought came to me that
maybe the people around me
were waiting for me."
"Waiting for me to be okay enough
to listen to their consoling words
that were well prepared in advance."
"That made me cry."
Hello?
Oh, tomorrow?
I understand.
Okay.
Clear my entire afternoon tomorrow.
I will, but why all of a sudden?
I have to attend the event
organized by Chairman Woo.
An event? Tomorrow?
You know how my father is.
In front of his investees,
he wants to brag about
his performance and network.
I got the call today.
We'll go and show that we're clapping.
Depending on the atmosphere,
we'll leave early.
Still, notifying us of the event
a day before is a bit rude.
Jeez.
Is the investor pulling a power move?
KOREA INVESTMENT CORPORATION
APPOINTS NEW EXECUTIVES
Korea Investment Corporation
will be hiring someone.
Vice President Lee Seok-jin
at Yuseong Finance.
RÉSUMÉ
I'll take care of the rest.
Just make the recommendation.
Ms. Kang.
You're growing well.
Ms. Kang looks very down today.
Is there something wrong?
I'm not sure.
The projects are going well
without problems.
There shouldn't be anything
to feel down about.
Lee Kwang-hee.
Did you do something wrong?
Why do you blame my darl…
Darl… ing?
Darling?
"Don't snarl at him."
Snarl, right?
You were gonna say, "Don't snarl at him."
Weren't you?
So, is that the slang these days?
Is that what you're saying?
Yes, yes.
Don't, don't snarl at him!
"Snarl," I see.
I thought I heard "darling." My ears--
I definitely heard a "D" in there.
I thought that Kyung-hwa
was calling Kwang-hee her darling.
Why would I?
No way.
- The door is open. It's open.
- Gosh.
Aren't you two getting in?
I forgot to bring some documents.
Gyu-rim, I need to check something.
- Wait a second.
- Okay.
Go ahead first.
See you tomorrow!
This whole "snarl" thing is fun.
Right? That was a total snarl, right?
Until when will they continue
acting like that?
Leave them be.
I'm having fun.
LIST OF STOCKHOLDERS
WOOMYUNG INVESTMENT
PERCENTAGE OF SHARE
45.6%
Is it because of tomorrow's event?
When Peoplez was founded,
Chairman Woo helped us a lot.
Without his help,
this company wouldn't even exist.
Now,
it feels like a burden.
Or am I being malicious?
Is his involvement excessive?
That's not it.
But at this rate,
if he puts his mind to it,
he could control Peoplez.
We can't let that happen.
I'm the one who started it,
and it's up to me to protect it.
I should do it.
Ms. Kang, look at me.
Just think about one thing.
It's you who founded and brought
Peoplez where it is today.
If it wasn't you,
no one could have led Peoplez.
You're doing very well.
So stop worrying.
And let me get off work.
What?
Everyone left.
WOOMYUNG INVESTMENT
Mr. Chairman.
Congratulations.
Thank you. It's all thanks to you.
Hey, Ms. Kang.
Over here.
I'll work hard.
I won't forget your support.
Father, Ms. Kang is here.
Hello, sir.
You're here.
I must be quite late.
Hello, Ms. Kim!
I'm sure you know each other.
Have you met Mr. Woo?
I met him a few times.
Good to see you, Mr. Woo.
I didn't expect to see you here.
I'm getting a lot of help
from the Chairman these days.
All right!
I invited you here today
for a special celebration.
Vice President Lee Seok-jin.
Vice President Lee Seok-jin
has become the vice president
at Korea Investment Corporation.
- Are you starting next week?
- Yes, sir.
He'll be a big help to our members.
I'm Lee Seok-jin.
I look forward to working with you.
Wait!
And Ms. Kim.
CEO Kim Hye-jin has worked
very hard on this.
You flatter me.
After all, it's my job to recommend
a good candidate who fits the position.
Please feel free to recommend me
any good candidate.
Everyone, make recommendations!
Wishing tremendous success to all of you.
Cheers!
- Cheers!
Wasn't Ms. Kang in charge of your work?
Is she not as good as she used to be?
If she wasn't competent,
she'd be gone already.
I wouldn't turn my back on her.
The only thing she can count on
is her brain.
If you're looking to hire, ask Ms. Kang.
Oh, Mr. Park
weren't you looking for a son-in-law?
Ms. Kang, find a man whom
Mr. Park would like as a son-in-law.
Does she find people like that too?
Can I ask you for a professional golfer
who gives private lessons?
Someone with a pretty face, if possible.
You'd better pay her a big commission.
- Father.
- Headhunters aren't anything special.
They just find people you need
for a commission.
Isn't that right, Ms. Kang?
It seems you still lack
an understanding of headhunters.
I should work harder.
I'm sorry, but that isn't my specialty.
Ms. Kang, why are you so serious?
Leave it to me.
I'll find someone that
you'd absolutely be delighted with.
Please excuse me.
I have another meeting to attend.
Yes, go ahead.
Stay until the end.
This is my event.
I think you're smart enough
to know your place,
Ms. Kang.
Over here!
Give her a drink.
Drink.
I'm Yu Eun-ho,
Ms. Kang Ji-yun's secretary.
I apologize.
I wasn't able to clear her schedule.
Ms. Kang needs to go to her next meeting.
Your loyalty is excessive.
You should know whether
it's your place to step in or not.
I apologize for being rude.
I learned that a secretary's priority is
the person he serves.
Let's go, Ms. Kang.
SPECIAL THANKS TO KIM SHIN-ROCK
You don't have to be perfect.
It's okay to look shabby.
However you are, I'll stay by your side.
CEO Min Jeong-hyuk.
He's the CEO of a successful
interior design company.
Are you free for dinner tonight?
Will Ms. Kang be interested in him?
Do you know each other?
We're comrades.
- Unrequited--
- It's nothing.
What's your relationship with Su-hyeon?
You have an eye for women.
Do you even know what she's like?
He texted to tell me
that he can't be at work today.
Is something wrong?
Today,
I met your father.
Subtitle translation by: Helena Noh